Guide to the Fredericka Martin Photograph Collection ALBA.PHOTO.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I: Photographs
  - Medical Personnel: Salle 9, Mataró, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Medical Personnel: Shipboard, Back Row (L to R) Dr. Castro, Caesare ?, Tate ?, ?; Middle Row (L to R), Edna Drabkin Romer, Fredericka Martin, ? Faller, May Edythe Dyer, Mary Rader, Selma Chadwick; Front Row (L to R), Dr., ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Medical Personnel: Showering Women, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, Angelita ?, Ferriouda Herrero, Pepita ?, Jerry ?, ?, Uiva ?, ?, ? Voloklein, ?, ?, ?, ?, Tarançon, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, Barcelona, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, Murcia, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, Saying Goodbye to John Jacob Posner and Staff, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, ?, Andrea Muniz, Petra Diaz, ?, ?, Constancia ?, Emelia ?, Villa Paz, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, ?, Rosita ?, Madrid, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, At the Beach, Port Bou, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Medical Personnel: Stretcher-Bearers, Villa Paz, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Medical Personnel: Surgery, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Medical Personnel: Valcarca Hospital, Barcelona, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Medical Tent: With Unidentified Woman, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Medical Vehicles: Ambulances from U.S., Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Memorials to International Brigade: Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Menhoff, Dr.: Group, ?, ?, ?, ?, ? (Women), Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Merims, Sonia: Group, ?, ?, ?, ?, ?, (Men), Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Merims, Sonia: George Moser and Spanish Children, Villa Paz, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Mexican Volunteer: Portrait, Villa Paz, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Militiamen: Marching, Valencia, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Miller, Benjamin: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Miller, William: Contact Sheet with Portrait of Miller, Edward Lending, Lester Gittleson, Johnny Bernard, Congressman Jerry O'Connel, undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Miller, William: Contact Sheet of Images from Miller's Photo Album, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Minor, Robert: Donald H. Pitts, Villa Paz, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Moser, George C.: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Murcia Hospital: Recovery Room, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Murcia Hospital: Treating a Patient, ca.1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Nance, Youngblood: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Oliva Campillo, Juan: Family, Spain, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Palestinian Nurse "Ruth": Poolside, University Hospital, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Palestinian Nurse "Ruth": Poolside with Spanish Youth, University Hospital, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Pasionara Hospital: Buildings, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pasionara Hospital: Ruth Epstein, Dora Donda, Hermine Hartman, Lisa Nommiot, Lisa Gavric, Edith ?, Hilda Bell, Murcia, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Paul Valliant Couturier: Children's Camp, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pelegrini, Antonio: In Operating Room, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Pelegrini, Antonio: Group, Manuel ?, Jose ?, Sitting on Ambulance, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Perez, Odio: Al Steine, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Perez, Odio: Group, Toby Jensky at Fiesta, Castillejo, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Pike, Florence (a.k.a. Florence Mildred Tew): En Route to Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Pike, Florence (a.k.a. Florence Mildred Tew): En Route to Spain, Rose Wachsman, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Pike, William: In Operating Room, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Pike, William: In Tree, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Pike, William: Shaking a Woman's Hand, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Pike, William: with Unidentified Woman, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Pike, William: with Wife, Post-SCW, U.S. [?], undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Pilar, Liam: Group, Unidentified Children and Men, Japan, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Pilar, Liam: Portrait, NYC, May 9, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Pilar, Liam: Unidentified Woman, Spain [?], ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Pitts, Donald H.: At the Front, Non-Combat, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Pitts, Donald H.: with Two Others, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Pitts, Donald H.: Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Pitts, Williams: At the Front, Non-Combat, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Pool, Nick: Groups, Unidentified, Vich, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Group, Jaw Surgery Patients, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Group, Lenora Temple, Mathilda Jankovic, Dulcea Hernaiz, Rebecca Shulman, Evelyn Rahman, Rose Weiner, Epiphanio Lopez, Jose Simon Gonzalez, Martha Mitchell, with Two Others, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Group, M. Zachary Stadt, Unidentified, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Group, Martha Mitchell and Patients, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Group, Martha Mitchell, M. Zachary Stadt and Unidentified Group, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Spanish Patient and Black Sheep, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Pozo Blanco: Unidentified Volunteers, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Pretecalle, Ojier: Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Purviance, Katherine: Group, Children, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Rackley, Mildred: Carol Rahman and Ambulance, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Rackley, Mildred: Family, Not in Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Rader, Mary: Shipboard, Unidentified Man, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Rauschwald, Mark: Demonstrations, NYC, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Rauschwald, Mark: Dombrowski Brigade, Barcelona, Jul 10, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Rauschwald, Mark: Paintings, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Rauschwald, Mark: Residence in NYC, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Raven, Robert J.: Kissing Fernanda Good-Bye, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Recovering Patients: General/Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Recovering Patients: Benicasim, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Reissing, Herman F.: Portrait with Wife, Not in Spain, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Roemer, Edna: Group, Jack Devine, Charles DeSevelskoe, Norman Rontz, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Roffman, Joe: Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Romer, Sam: Portrait, Not in Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - El Romeral: Nursing School, Tarancon, [1970s] (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - El Romeral Hospital: Buildings, Tarancon, Summer 1937 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - El Romeral Hospital: (Center) Helen Freeman, Mildred Rackley (Left) Anne Taft (Right) Pierre Queignac (Front) Rose Freed, Ray Harris, Fredericka Martin, Tarancon, Feb 16, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - El Romeral Hospital: Laboratory/Pharmacy, Tarancon, Feb 1937 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - El Romeral Hospital: Male Nurses Aides Making Plaster Bandages, Tarancon, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Rubin, Henry: Groups, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Rubin, Henry: Mobile Blood Transfusion Unit, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Rubin, Henry: Operating Room, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Rubin, Henry: Portraits, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Ruiz, Jose: Ambulance Driver, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Saelices Hospital: Children's Festival, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Salon: Almira, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Sanchez, Ramon: Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Saulhen, Frank: At the Front, Non-Combat, Cordoba Front, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Schuetrum, Walter J.: At the Front, Non-Combat, Juan ?, Pete Smith, "Southgate", Mac Kraus, ?, Hal Smith, ? Govett, Spain, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Schuldiner, Anne: Shipboard, Two Nurses and ?, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Schulman, Rebecca: Family and Friends, undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Schuman, Rebecca: Group, Irving Busch, Ramen Durem and Four Others, Villa Paz, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Schulman, Rebecca: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Schuman, Rebecca: Unidentified Man, Not in Spain, [1935] (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Schuman, Rebecca: Unidentified Man and Woman, Villa Paz, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Schulman, Rebecca: Unidentified Nurses, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Seminar Hospital: Tarançon, Dec 1937 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Service Internationale pour l'Enfance: Group, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Shipboard: Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Shuldiner, Anne: Shipboard with Two Nurses and One Man, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Silverstein, Esther: Portrait, Murcia, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Siqueiros, David Alfaro: Mural, [Mexico], undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Smith, Bill: Portrait with Unidentified Man, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Smith, John: Portrait, NYC, undated (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Smithson, Beryl: Michael [Erceg ?], Belcazar Hospital, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Soler y Tarafa, Oscar: En Route to Spain, Family Farewell, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Sonnenberg, Randall: Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Spanish Army Hospitals: Baeza, Ubeda, Jaen Province, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Barcelona, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Benicasim, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Castillejo, Segóbriaga, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Figueras, Jun 1937 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Godella, Aug 1937 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Madrid, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Photographic Postcards, Madrid, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Murcia, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Tarançon, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Valencia, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Spanish Civilians, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Spanish Civilians: Almeria, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Spanish Civilians: Children, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Spanish Civilians: Children, Benicasim, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Spanish Civilians: Shepherd, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Spanish Civilians: Workers, Laundrywomen, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Spanish Civilians: Workers, Laundrywomen and M. Zachary Stadt, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Spanish Landscapes, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Spanish Landscapes: Murcia, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Spanish Landscapes: Puy Del Mas, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Spanish Landscapes: Sabinosa, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Spanish Landscapes: Villa Paz, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Spanish Nurse: Portrait, Murcia, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Spanish Nurses: Groups, Murcia, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Spanish Villages: Street Scenes, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Sparrow, ?: with Six Men, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Sparrow, ?: with Unidentified Woman, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Stadt, M. Zachary: Group, Hilda Bell (Roberts), ? Gomez, ? Prieto, ? Balans, Shipboard on S.S. Normandie, May 1937 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Stander, Lionel: Collecting Funds for Medical Supplies, U.S., ca.1937- 1938 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Stirchbaum, Max: Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Straus, Mark: Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Straus, Mark: Unidentified Doctor, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Straus, Mark: with Patient, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Student Nurses: Group, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Sueco Noruego Hospital: Buildings, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Sueco Noruego Hospital: Medical Personnel, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Swienczewski, Walter: Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Taft, Anne: At the Front, Non-Combat, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Taft, Anne: Behind the Lines, Rest and Relaxation, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Taft, Anne: May Edith Dyer, May Levine, Grace Margolis, Mataró, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Taft, Anne: Group, Unidentified, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Taft, Anne: Portrait, Not in Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Taft, Anne: Portrait, U.S., ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Taft, Anne: Surgery, A. I. Friedman and Albert Byrne, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Telfuentes, Dr.: Presenting at Panel, U.S., ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Temple, Lenora: Portrait, [Spain?], ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Temple, Lenora: Shipboard, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Tenin, Juliette: Medical Personnel, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Tenin, Juliette: Portraits, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Thompson, Louise: Portraits, U.S., undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Toch, Joseph: Portraits, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Torman, Alexander: Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Towsen, Gus: Shipboard with Two Men, NYC, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Train Station: Cerbere (France), May 28, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Unidentified Group: Benicasim, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - University Hospital: Lisa Gavric, Anka Bohimicki, Olga "Milica" Å½ivkovic, Murcia, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Urmston, Lillian: Operation, Teruel Front, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Van Reemst, Theodore: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Van Reemst de Vries, Trudi: Portrait, Post SCW, undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Van Reemst de Vries, Trudi: Receiving Award/Flowers, undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Vanzant, Frances: with Sylvia Sidney, U.S., ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Vanzant, Frances: Group, Unidentified, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Vanzant, Frances: Portraits, NYC and Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Vega-Diaz, Francisco: Hospital de Andujar, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Veterans: Post-SCW, Edward O'Flaherty, William Pike, Tom ?, Daniel Samuel Groden, Oscar Hunter, Charles O'Flaherty, Not in Spain, undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Village Fair: Child with Banner, "Milk for the Children of Spain!", NYC, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Villa John Reed: Benicasim, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Villa Paz, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Villa Paz: Ambulance, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Villa Paz: Cleaning/Kitchen Staff, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Villa Paz: Flag Donated by the French, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Villa Paz, Groups, Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Villa Paz: Individuals, Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Villa Paz: Operating Room, Apr 1937 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Villa Paz: Post-SCW, undated (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Villa Paz: Recovering Patients, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Vogel, Sidney: Behind the Lines, Rest and Relaxation, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Vogel, Sidney: Group, with Five Men, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Unknown Man: In Small Boat, Cerbere (France), May 1937 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Vogel, Sidney: Portraits, Spain, undated, Nov 1937 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Wachsman, Rose: Family, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Wachsman, Rose: Portrait, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Wachsman, Rose: Rest and Relaxation, Unidentified Man, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Wachsman, Shipboard, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Wagnon, Alice Elizabeth: Group, Leonard H. Larson and Evelyn Andell, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Wagnon, Alice Elizabeth: Group, Unidentified, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Warton, Patrice: Group, in Vineyard, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Weber, Franz: Gurs Concentration Camp, France, undated (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Weinstein, (?): Reading, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Weissman, Helene: Behind the Lines, Daily Life of the Soldiers, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Weissman, Helene: Behind the Lines, Rest and Relaxation, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Weissman, Helene: Shipboard with Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Weissman, Helene: With Oscar Israel Weissman, Villa Paz, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Weissman, Oscar Israel: with Two Men, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Wesson, Helene: Daily Life of the Soldiers, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Wilson, Una: With Unidentified Man, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Zandt, N.: Group, Three Volunteers and One Boy, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Zwnais, Jack: Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 100)
- Series II: Negatives
  - Alcoy Hospital: Buildings, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Allemand, Klaus: Artwork, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - AMB: Ambulance/Autochir, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - AMB: Ambulance Donated by the Negro People of America to the People of Republican Spain, Salaria Kee (a.k.a. Salaria Kea) (second from right), ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - AMB: Chauffeurs/Drivers, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - AMB: Demonstrations/Fund Raising, Not in Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - AMB: Dentists, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - AMB: Doctors and Nurses, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - AMB: En Route to Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - AMB: En Route to Spain, Ambulance Unit No. VII, Back Row, Council Carter, Cezar Ferreiro Labrador, Wayne Taine, Joseph Dhago, Edna Drabkin Romer, Thelma Erickson, Sessie Henderson (Fuller), Edythe May Dyer, Mary Rader, Selma Chadwick, Seated, Joseph Highkin, Samuel Franklin, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - AMB: En Route to Spain, Ambulance Unit No. VII, Thelma Erickson Edythe May Dyer, Dr. Franklin, Selma Chadwick, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - AMB: En Route to Spain, Hilda Bell, A.N. Townsen, Joseph Richard Chodoff, Rose Margaret Harvan, S.S. Normandie, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - AMB: Frank Thomas Woodbury, Leo Eloesser, Edward Barsky and Unidentified Group, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - AMB: Groups, Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - AMB: Individuals, Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - AMB: Two Women in Spain, Evelyn Hutchins Rahman and Ruth Davidow, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - At the Front: Non-Combat, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - At the Front: Non-Combat, Toby Jensky, Odio Perez and Unidentified Group, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Barsky, Edward, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Behind the Lines: Daily Life of the Soldiers, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Behind the Lines: Daily Life of the Soldiers, Dutch Volunteers, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Behind the Lines: Rest and Relaxation, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Behind the Lines: Rest and Relaxation, ?, Judson Briggs, ?, Dave Davidson, Barcelona, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 22a)
  - Behind the Lines: Rest and Relaxation, Albert Byrne and Thelma Erickson, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Behind the Lines: Rest and Relaxation, Karl Rahman, Evelyn Hutchins with Three Others, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Bell, Hilda: Images from Photo Album, Murcia, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Benicasim Hospital, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Bombed/Shelled Buildings, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Briggs, Judson: Groups and Portrait, Spain, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Epstein, Ruth, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - El Escorial Hospital: Buildings, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Fuhr (DeVries), Lini: (center) and Unidentified Group, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Goland, Philip Pakier, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Groups: Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Hecht, Anne, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Homenaje, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Hospital: Recovery Ward, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Individuals: Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Injured/Recovering Patients, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Medical Personnel: Dutch, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Medical Personnel: En Route to Spain, ? Murhy, ? Faubion, Morris Miller, ? Lockett, ? Goldrick, ? Vazquez, ? Hansen, ? Bleir, ? Ransom, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Medical Personnel: Groups, Unidentified, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Medical Personnel: Surgery, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Medical Personnel: Surgery, Albert Byrne, Anne Taft and Oscar Weissman, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Militiawomen, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Miller, William Colfax: Certificada de Baja, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Posters/Artwork, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Refugees, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Spanish Civilians, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Spanish Civilians: Children, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Spanish Civilians: Women, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Van Reemst de Vries, Trudi: Portrait, ca.1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Silde: Latin American Woman and Child, undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Series III: Photo Albums
  - Red Photo Album, ca.1937-1938 (Box 8)
  - Green Photo Album, ca.1937-1938 (Box 8)
- Series IV: Addendum (2012)
  - Briggs, Judson: Painting, "Girl With Necklace", undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - AMB: First Unit Landing At Le Havre, June 1937 (Box OS006, Folder 1, Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Ambulances/Mobile Hospitals -- Europe - En Route to Spain, ca. 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Ambulances/Mobile Hospitals -- U.S., ca. 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Ambulances/Mobile Hospitals - Spain, ca. 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - At the Front: "Bringing the Wounded to the Rear, After the Battle", ca. 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - At the Front: Soldiers Charging (Spanish Civil War), ca. 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ayers, Frank and Anita, June 6, 1953; 1969; undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Ayers, Frank - Holiday Card, ca. 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Barsky, Dr. Edward; Rebecca Schulman, [Rodofo - Rudolph?], ["Sabateur & Agent ?"], ca. 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Bombed/Shelled Buildings: Valencia -- Group of Houses Destroyed by Italian Bombers, October 3, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Cordoba, ca. 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Fuhr (de Vries), Lini - Portrait, ca. 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Hospital: Unidentified Hospital Interior (Spain), ca. 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Jake Cohen's Home, January 1974 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee. Joaquin Gudino Flores, Miguel Negrin, Dr. Edward Barsky, Nickolai Zimenkov, Dr. Bedrich Syrovy, ca. 1943 - 1944 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Luba [Luba Bresher?], undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Refugees (Spain), ca. 1936-1938 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Reger, Muriel, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Taft, Anne and Helen Feinberg At Party, ca. 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 20)